imperfectwomen.com 2012-05-23

# Privacy Policy | Imperfect Women | Celebrity, Style, Women's Health, Relationships, Career, Parenting, Women, Food and Politics

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you leave a comment on a post. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes only.

When leaving a comment on a post on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google may, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to this sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Comments – In order to enhance their use of Imperfect Women, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. Commenters may register anonymously. However, if a third party complains that a comment breaches our Terms of Use (e.g. libels them), then in accordance with our Terms of Use, we will make reasonable efforts to contact the commenter and alert them to the situation. If we are required to by law to disclose commenters’ contact information, we will attempt to contact commenters to give them the opportunity to respond to such requests. Please refer to our Terms of Use for more information.

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Guidelines regarding children**

Personal information about children is a concern for all of us. At Imperfect Women, we take the protection of children’s privacy very seriously.Imperfect Women does not encourage participation or visitation by children. Imperfect Women contains non-children’s content and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen. Anyone under the age of eighteen is discouraged from participating in any sex related chats.

If you are under 18, you may use Imperfect Women only with involvement of a parent or guardian. Imperfect Women reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel orders in their sole discretion.

**Guidelines for use**

Imperfect Women reserves the right to refuse service and remove or edit content as we see necessary. Swearing is discouraged and most likely will be deleted.Personal attacks are not allowed.No bullying or threats allowed.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [**Imperfect Women**.](http://www.imperfectwomen.com/terms/)

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

From time to time, changes may be made to the privacy policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. A visitor or member is bound by any changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted.

This policy was last modified on 03/19/2011

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.imperfectwomen.com/

info@imperfectwomen.com

2080 Century Park East  
Los Angeles, CA 90067  
Suite 903

When linking to another site, a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site
